Чинацу сенпай мен Харию сенпай?
Олар, жай ғана достар!
Қара, бізде бірге жүрміз ғой!
Дұрыс айтасың!
Жай ғана үйге қайтып бара жатыр!
Иә иә.
Иә иә!
Не?
Екеуі де жұлдыз.
Сонымен…
Олар әрі сыныптас, әрі бір партада отырады.
Және екеуі де сынып өкілдері.
-Дым қағып тұрған жоқпын.
-Амансың ба?
СЫНЫПТАС, БІР ПАРТА, БІРГЕ ӨКІЛ
Уайымдай берме!
Чинацу сенпай баскетболға ғана көңіл бөлемін деді ғой!
Солай шығар.
Бірақ, ғашықтық сезімді жай ғана ұстап тұра алмайсың!
Бір жағынан дұрыс.
Қалжыңдап тұрған жоқсың ба?
Көп қорап
Көк қорап
3-бөлім
Чии
Осы жылғылар қалай екен?
Үшінші жылғылар мен Харию көш бастап тұр.
Хариюдің орны бір бөлек болар?
Оның ұлттық жарысқа баруға мүмкіндігі бар.
Бірақ өз басым, оған үлкен үміт артамын.
Кешірім өтінем, доп кетіп қалды!
Чинацу сенпай!
Сенпайды көргенде, кешегі есіме түсіп кетеді.
-Жақсы.
-Анау!
Тайки-кұн, жаттығуың нешеде бітеді?
Кілтті үйде ұмытып кеттіппін.
Және үйдегілер кеш келеміз деді.
7:00-де.
-Бізде біреу-міреу естіп қойса не болады?
-Менің де жаттығуымда жетіде бітеді.
-Сосын--
-Чии.
Сендерде артық таймер бар ма?
-Біздікі сынып қалды.
-Чии?
Бізде жоқ-ау.
Солай дееее...
Қазір ғана, ол Чинацу сенпайды "Чи" деді ме?
Қығанғаным-ай!
Олар қаншалықты жақын?
Мен жай Чинацу демеймін, міндетті
түрде "сенпай" деп қоса айтамын!
-Чии!
-Plus!
-Yes?
-She seems okay with it.
-Hey, Chii!
-Hi!
What would I have to do to call her that?
-May I call you Chii?
-Yes.
INOMATA
Since they're classmates?
Since they sit together?
Or is it because
they're both superstars on their teams?
I'm so lame.
There's no point dwelling on this.
There's nothing I can do.
I can never be the same grade as her.
Even if she told me I could call her Chii,
I couldn't.
If we didn't live together…
if we weren't in such close proximity…
I wouldn't be struggling with this.
Chi… na… tsu--
-I'm home.
-Senpai!
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm such a creep!
Lame plus creep equals me!
You got home fast.
When I was heading home,
the badminton players
were just going into their clubroom.
You said practice ended at 7:00,
but I guess it ran long.
What is wrong with me?
All she did was say "badminton players,"
and all I'm thinking is that she means
Haryu Senpai.
-Sorry, I'll go to my room.
-Wait.
Sorry.
I wanted to ask you something.
I'll be embarrassed
if I'm wrong about this.
But did you run home?
I noticed you sweating,
so I thought maybe you did.
Is that because
I went home earlier than you
and you didn't want
to keep me waiting outside?
-How did she notice that?
-I did wait at school.
All I've done is worry about
what to call her.
But knowing how carefully
she was watching me,
makes me so happy that
I don't care about that anymore.
If you did,
nice save.
No, you're wrong!
I just thought I'd squeeze
in training on the way home!
You know, I think I'll go on another run!
This living situation
is just messing with my head.
I'm no match for him anyway.
It doesn't matter who she's with,
or what they call her.
If I start worrying about that,
I'll go crazy.
Right now, I need to focus
on the intradepartmental matches.
But hearing him call her "Chii"
might still get to me.
In! Game! Inomata!
You won again? You're on a roll.
Yeah.
But I've basically only faced first-years.
I haven't played any starters yet.
Besides…
It looks like Haryu Senpai
won every match.
That reminds me.
What was the deal
with Chinatsu Senpai and Haryu Senpai?
About that…
It doesn't matter what's between them,
I won't let it get to me anymore!
Sounds like you already failed.
Oh, well.
I feel weird being a senpai.
-I don't care!
-Then why are you turning around?
The badminton team
is running scrimmages, right?
Yeah, and he's won all his matches.
Only so far.
So modest.
We still have more games.
It's just the start.
I see. Good luck.
Thanks.
I don't care.
You two have been awful chummy lately.
You've been hanging out with Kano a lot.
We do sit next to each other in class.
Yeah? Is that all?
-That's all.
-He's melting.
We're both busy with sports.
But…
there's something nice
about seeing a girl work hard.
-Wait, are you saying…?
-No.
Oh, boy.
This is some bad timing.
Love-all. Play.
In. Five-one.
Haryu's dictating the pace.
He doesn't let you attack.
He's like a brick wall.
Is he okay? This looks really one-sided.
What's he gonna do?
They're on different levels.
And he has a whole year
of experience over him.
This has to be tough.
Facing an opponent
who's close to his crush.
Someone who might even like her too.
Plus, he's closer to achieving his goals.
With such a clear display of dominance,
it's like he's being told
to give up on both.
-Natsu!
-Coming!
In. Eleven-four.
Looks like another win for Haryu.
Man, he's strong.
Can someone beat him already?
You okay? Drink some water.
Hey.
Wasn't I super close on that last one?
I was slow getting back in position.
I have trouble staying active.
You seem charged up.
I got my run in before this.
Not that.
I thought you'd be more bothered.
Like, about what happened earlier.
I do have to thank Chinatsu Senpai
for motivating me even more.
I never want to use her
as an excuse for when I lose.
It's not like I play badminton
only for her sake.
Deep down,
I just love badminton.
Taiki. Clock's ticking.
Coming!
Still, I need to adjust.
I decided I'm going for it.
I have to keep pushing forward.
One step at a time.
Nice return.
But he hit it back.
Hang in there, Taiki!
One step.
It's up.
Close one.
You started rallying.
But you should be happy.
You may have lost to Haryu Senpai,
but that performance
will get you on the team.
You don't look happy.
I mean, I lost.
And those points I got
in the second half felt scrappy.
He dictated the pace
throughout the whole match.
BURNABLE TRASH
I knew that Haryu Senpai was tough.
But I'm still frustrated I lost.
You hear that?
That little punk.
I'm the one who's frustrated.
Why? You won.
Because at the end…
What? You can't leave me hanging!
Come on, tell me!
Of course it's not just going to work out.
I was facing Haryu Senpai after all.
He's got me beat
in technique, speed, and power.
I need to play more aggressively.
And read my opponent for better placement.
I have to smash any easy shots.
I need to build more experience
to pull that off.
I'm not practicing enough at all.
Taiki!
Follow me!
Chinatsu Senpai?
The sun will set soon. Come on, hurry up!
Wait, where are we going?
Someplace nice!
I mean, I guess it's nice.
But why the park?
Well…
Ta-da! I borrowed these.
Why did you borrow badminton rackets?
You said we should play sometime.
She remembered!
Besides, I figured you'd want
to practice some more.
I'm usually most motivated
right after a game.
I thought you might be the same.
Having someone
who understands how you feel
is really nice.
Ready?
You can't even hit it?
No, I'm just not good at serves!
You're moving your left hand too much.
The left hand just drops it
and the racket does the rest.
That was perfect advice!
You're acting too surprised.
But this will just be practice for me.
You should do smashes.
It's fine.
I hit enough during the match.
I was watching your match against Haryu.
Please erase that from your memory.
Why?
Because it's embarrassing.
Since I lost.
It's not embarrassing.
You started landing
those smashes towards the end.
Yeah, but…
Besides, at the interval
of the second game,
it was eleven-four.
And in the time it took him
to score another 10 points to get to 21,
you scored 11 points.
What?
But a loss is a loss!
He totally outplayed me in the first half.
It doesn't matter how much
I scored the second half.
I still lost.
What are you laughing at?
Sorry.
You really hate losing, don't you?
Don't swing with your upper body!
Use your legs!
Yes, sir!
Whenever someone gives you instructions,
you work on it
all throughout morning practice.
Even during your match against Haryu,
you never gave up.
That's why you scored in the second half.
So don't worry.
You'll be fine!
Being so untalented,
it's hard for me to believe in myself.
I'll win next time.
That's the spirit!
But I can easily believe
anything the person I like says.
YUKIKO
It's from Yukiko.
My mom?
She's asking what time we'll be home.
"Chii"?
Is that from Haryu Senpai?
Don't tell me he gave that to her.
Oh, this?
They're from my classmates.
They call me "Chii" in class.
So it wasn't a pet name
only Haryu Senpai uses.
Chinatsu Senpai has always been
so approachable.
Maybe she really isn't interested
in any kind of romance right now.
Ready to go?
Go on ahead without me.
There will be a lot of people around…
and while it might not bother you at all,
it's a little embarrassing to walk back
to the same house with a girl.
I'll do a few more practice swings.
"It might not bother you," huh?
So that's how it seems to him.
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
What? Why?
DOUBLES
HARYU AND INOMATA
I'm playing doubles with Haryu Senpai?
But I'm trying to take him down.
Yeah.
Going to nationals
with your romantic rival sounds awkward.
Even disregarding the fact
I like Chinatsu Senpai, I--
Taiki.
Let's practice.
Okay.
You'll be following a regimen
I come up with for the time being.
Thank goodness.
It doesn't seem like he overheard that.
So…
you like Chinatsu Kano, huh?
How interesting.
This is the worst start
a doubles pair can have!
Way too slow!
You're lagging!
Okay!
Haryu is one tough dude.
They did running, circuit training,
and footwork exercises before this.
I'd be puking by now.
You getting tired yet?
Tell me if you need a break.
I can't have you passing out.
But… I've never seen Chii
whine about being too tired.
I bet any guy she ends up dating
will be cool and tough like her.
What shall we do next?
Rotation practice. Five two-minute reps.
You look like a mushroom
growing from the desk.
And not a nutritious one.
Shut up.
He's been physically working me
to death over the last week.
The classroom
is the only place I can rest.
-What about home?
-I'm surprised.
I didn't think Haryu Senpai
would work with you so much.
He didn't seem like the team player type.
So this Haryu Senpai
is the guy who was walking home
with Chinatsu Senpai, right?
So maybe he's like…
"Don't make a move on my girl,"
and messing with you.
You're beneath me.
He's trying to make you give up
by putting you in your place.
The truth is, I do feel inferior to him.
Even though we do the same regimen,
his speed never slows down,
and his shots are so accurate.
I bet badminton is fun when you have
such a great physical foundation.
Badminton freak.
Masochist.
Those are insults.
Taiki.
Why did you hit a cross shot there?
The opponent was setting up a backhand.
A straight shot would've had
more speed too.
You should've gone for it,
even in an awkward position.
If you only settle for the easy shots,
you'll never improve.
Right!
I survived another day.
Is this a battlefield?
I need a drink.
Of juice, right?
Taiki!
Good work today.
You too!
Those are second-year students.
And Chinatsu Senpai.
I actually got paired up
to play doubles with this guy.
You're talking about me here?
He's still a first-year
and absolutely garbage.
He's still got so many holes in his game.
He sucks at shot selection
and blunders when he rushes in to attack.
I can't deny any of it because it's true.
But…
I think Taiki's going to be good.
This kid doesn't fold at all,
no matter how much I bully him.
Even when I subject him to stuff
that I think is a little too much,
he actually finishes all of it.
What?
You're such a sadist.
You're always tough
on people you believe in.
-That's not true.
-I'm glad.
At least he sees some potential in me.
You ignore people you don't care about.
You're doing great.
Just the other day, you know
that first-year I'm looking after?
It's nice being acknowledged
by the older students.
I had a message from my girlfriend.
Girlfriend, huh?
You have a girlfriend?
-Yeah, since last week.
-Last week?
I liked her for a long time,
but she's in show business.
I was just about to give up
when she asked me out.
She's so cool.
She's been working hard
chasing her dream since she was little.
Chii, thanks for the other day.
I would've felt awkward
going to buy makeup on my own.
Don't mention it.
He was just toying with me
this whole time!
Looks like it'll be a while
before you get a girlfriend.
Nobody asked you!
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto